[English subtitles are available]
[الترجمة الإنجليزية متوفرة]
[Hello There]
[أهلاً بك]
[Episode 15]
[الحلقة 15]
Did you remember anything?
هل تذكرت شيئا؟
Yes.
نعم.
Great!
عظيم!
Yan.
يان.
You finally remembered.
لقد تذكرت أخيرًا.
I did.
فعلتُ.
You knocked me off my feet.
لقد خلعتني عن قدمي.
You are really like what my cousin said.
أنت حقًا مثل ما قاله ابن عمي.
Brother-in-law. My advice to you is to be a gentleman.
شقيق الزوج.  نصيحتي لك هي أن تكون رجل نبيل.
Otherwise, I'll teach you how to be a gentleman now.
وإلا سأعلمك كيف تكون رجل نبيل الآن.
Yan.
يان.
Mr. Li.
السيد.  لي.
Please behave yourself.
يرجى تتصرف نفسك.
Stop harassing my fiancée!
توقف عن مضايقة خطيبتي!
Let go of her!
اتركها!
What?
ماذا؟
You want to knock him off his feet too?
هل تريد أن تطرده من قدميه أيضًا؟
Yan.
يان.
Mr. Li.
السيد.  لي.
Yan is a naive and lively girl.
يان فتاة ساذجة وحيوية.
She might have offended you.
ربما تكون قد أساءت إليك.
But as a man,
لكن كرجل ،
how can you hurt her, a girl?
كيف تؤذيها يا فتاة؟
It's none of your business.
هذا ليس من شأنك.
Yan is my fiancée.
يان خطيبتي.
Her business is my business.
عملها هو عملي.
Did you get hurt?
هل تأذيت؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
I mean before.
أعني من قبل.
That's good.
هذا جيد.
As long as I'm here,
طالما أنا هنا ،
I won't let him bully you again.
لن أسمح له بالتنمر عليك مرة أخرى.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Young Master.
المعلم الصغير.
It's my fault.
هذا خطأي.
I failed to stall Li Jian.
لقد فشلت في إيقاف لي جيان.
It doesn't matter.
لا يهم.
Young Master.
المعلم الصغير.
This time, the plan failed.
هذه المرة ، فشلت الخطة.
What are you going to do next?
ماذا ستفعل بعد ذلك؟
As for the rest,
أما الباقي ،
I can do it myself.
أستطيع أن أفعل ذلك بنفسي.
Yes.
نعم.
Dear Li.
عزيزي لي.
Have something.
احصل على شيء.
I heard about what happened during the day.
سمعت عما حدث خلال النهار.
Don't be too sad.
لا تحزن كثيرا.
You see.
هل ترى.
Since Tang Buyan has already forgotten about you,
منذ أن نسي تانغ بويان أمرك بالفعل ،
why don't you consider me?
لماذا لا تعتبرني
I won't give up on her.
لن أتخلى عنها.
Please leave, Manager Shen.
من فضلك اترك المدير شين.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
I hope you can still be this persistent
أتمنى أن تظل بهذا الإصرار
in a few days.
في أيام قليلة.
Manager.
مدير.
There are so many good men.
هناك الكثير من الرجال الطيبين.
Why does it have to be him?
لماذا يجب أن يكون هو؟
Don't you think it's so sexy
ألا تعتقد أنه مثير للغاية
when he turns me down?
عندما يرفضني؟
Yes.
نعم.
He came from the sky
لقد جاء من السماء
and held me, and we twirled in the air.
وأمسكني ، ولفنا في الهواء.
I'm so in love!
أنا واقع في الحب!
Dear Li.
عزيزي لي.
Mr. Li.
السيد.  لي.
What do you want with my fiancée
ماذا تريد مع خطيبتي
in the middle of the night?
في منتصف الليل؟
A haunting ghost!
شبح مخيف!
Same to you.
ولك مثله.
Dear Li.
عزيزي لي.
What are you thinking about at this late hour?
ما الذي تفكر فيه في هذه الساعة المتأخرة؟
Do you know what love is?
هل تعرف ما هو الحب؟
Love?
حب؟
Love is not something you say.
الحب ليس شيئا تقوله.
It's something you make.
إنه شيء تصنعه.
Dear Li,
عزيزي لي ،
why don't we go back to our room and discuss it?
لماذا لا نعود إلى غرفتنا ونناقشها؟
You're right.
أنت على حق.
Yan and I
يان وأنا
have gone through life and death several times.
مروا بالحياة والموت عدة مرات.
The feelings between us
المشاعر بيننا
have long been beyond mere words.
لطالما كانت أبعد من مجرد الكلمات.
But she doesn't remember anything.
لكنها لا تتذكر أي شيء.
Even if her memory is gone,
حتى لو ذهبت ذاكرتها ،
our feelings are still there.
مشاعرنا لا تزال موجودة.
Really?
حقًا؟
Then why would she be so cruel to you?
إذن لماذا تكون قاسية عليك؟
There are so many women in the world.
هناك الكثير من النساء في العالم.
Why does it have to be her?
لماذا يجب أن تكون هي؟
Why don't you look at others?
لماذا لا تنظر للآخرين؟
Such as me.
مثل لي.
The night is still young.
الليل لا يزال شابا.
Why don't we...
لماذا لا ...
Manager Shen.
مدير شين.
Why are you so obsessed with me?
لماذا أنت مهووس بي؟
I will never give up on Yan.
لن أتخلى عن يان أبدًا.
But why?
لكن لماذا؟
Whether it's her appearance, figure, or wealth,
سواء كان مظهرها أو شكلها أو ثروتها ،
she's nothing compared to me.
انها لا شيء مقارنة بي.
She doesn't need to compete with anyone.
لا تحتاج إلى التنافس مع أي شخص.
I like her
انا معجب بها
because she is who she is.
لأنها من هي.
That's it.
هذا كل شيء.
It's just because she's who she is.
هذا فقط لأنها هي.
Fine.
بخير.
I'll help you this time.
سأساعدك هذه المرة.
But whether you can get Tang Buyan back
ولكن ما إذا كان يمكنك استعادة Tang Buyan
is up to you.
هذا راجع إليك.
Cousin.
ابن عم.
Brother, we need to talk.
أخي ، نحن بحاجة للتحدث.
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
Yan.
يان.
If I can cure your blood vessel disease,
إذا كان بإمكاني علاج مرض الأوعية الدموية لديك ،
can you not marry Li Jian?
لا يمكنك الزواج من لي جيان؟
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Don't blame me if you don't leave now.
لا تلومني إذا لم تغادر الآن.
Are you really going to marry him
هل ستتزوجه حقًا؟
when you haven't retrieved your memories?
متى لم تسترجع ذكرياتك؟
Yan.
يان.
Go to the Serene Valley with me.
اذهب معي إلى وادي سيرين.
We'll look for the second half of the Book of Yueque.
سنبحث عن النصف الثاني من كتاب Yueque.
Maybe that book can solve your blood vessel disease.
ربما يمكن لهذا الكتاب أن يحل مرض الأوعية الدموية.
The Book of Yueque?
كتاب يويكي؟
The book
الكتاب
that you stole from my house?
التي سرقتها من منزلي؟
That book was given to me
هذا الكتاب أعطيت لي
by you personally.
بواسطتك شخصيا.
Would you like to give it a try?
هل تريد أن تجربها؟
If not,
ان لم،
I won't harass you ever again.
لن أضايقك مرة أخرى.
It looks like
يبدو
I have to make her think of me.
علي أن أجعلها تفكر بي
Do you remember
هل تذكر
what happened here?
ماذا حدث هنا؟
Tang Buyan.
تانغ بويان.
I think
أظن
I'm really falling in love with you.
أنا حقا أقع في حبك.
What should I do?
ماذا علي أن أفعل؟
Li Chengxi.
لي تشنغسي.
I...
أنا...
I think
أظن
I'm really falling in love with you.
أنا حقا أقع في حبك.
What should I do?
ماذا علي أن أفعل؟
Li Chengxi.
لي تشنغسي.
I...
أنا...
I think
أظن
I'm really falling in love with you.
أنا حقا أقع في حبك.
What should I do?
ماذا علي أن أفعل؟
Li Chengxi.
لي تشنغسي.
I...
أنا...
I think
أظن
I'm really falling in love with you.
أنا حقا أقع في حبك.
What should I do?
ماذا علي أن أفعل؟
Li Chengxi.
لي تشنغسي.
I...
أنا...
Yan.
يان.
I think
أظن
I'm really falling in love with you.
أنا حقا أقع في حبك.
Yan.
يان.
Yan?
يان؟
Did she have any serious illness before?
هل كانت تعاني من أي مرض خطير من قبل؟
That's it.
هذا كل شيء.
She was stimulated so that the disease was triggered.
تم تحفيزها حتى يتم تشغيل المرض.
You can't stimulate her anymore.
لا يمكنك تحفيزها بعد الآن.
Otherwise, her condition will get worse.
وإلا فإن حالتها ستزداد سوءًا.
And she won't live for three months.
ولن تعيش لمدة ثلاثة أشهر.
Boss!
رئيس!
Is this what you want?
هل هذا ما تريد؟
You keep saying you like her.
أنت تستمر بالقول أنك معجب بها.
And you don't care about her life?
وأنت لا تهتم بحياتها؟
Do you want her to remember that she loves you
هل تريدها أن تتذكر أنها تحبك
and die,
و مت،
or let her
أو دعها
live happily forever.
عش بسعادة إلى الأبد.
If you really like Yan,
إذا كنت تحب يان حقًا ،
please don't
من فضلك لا تفعل
show up in front of her ever again.
تظهر أمامها مرة أخرى.
How is she?
كيف حالها؟
If you want to know,
إذا أردت أن تعرف،
go check her out for yourself.
اذهب لتفقدها بنفسك.
What?
ماذا؟
You are going to give up in just two days?
سوف تستسلم في غضون يومين فقط؟
I can't just watch her
لا يمكنني مشاهدتها فقط
die like this.
يموت مثل هذا.
But it's not the first day that Tang Buyan
لكن هذا ليس اليوم الأول الذي يتواجد فيه تانغ بويان
has had her blood vessel disease.
كان لديها مرض الأوعية الدموية.
Brother Yan told me
أخبرني الأخ يان
that the Book of Yueque
أن كتاب يويكي
may cure her disease.
قد يعالج مرضها.
But whether the second part of the book
ولكن ما إذا كان الجزء الثاني من الكتاب
is in the valley
في الوادي
or whether that book can cure her,
أو ما إذا كان هذا الكتاب يمكن أن يعالجها ،
I'm not sure.
لست متأكد.
I can't let her take the risk again.
لا يمكنني السماح لها بالمخاطرة مرة أخرى.
I couldn't wish more that you would give up on her.
لا أستطيع أن أتمنى أن تتخلى عنها أكثر.
Then I'll have a chance with you.
ثم سأحظى بفرصة معك.
Oh, right.
صحيح.
This book
هذا الكتاب
is for you.
إنه لك.
I hope
آمل
you won't use it.
لن تستخدمه.
[36 Tactics to Pursue Your Wife]
[36 تكتيكات لملاحقة زوجتك]
♫Your figure is very thin♫
♫ شكلك نحيف جدا ♫
♫Choking up, I look even weaker♫
♫ الاختناق ، أبدو أضعف
♫It won't help♫
♫ لن يساعد ♫
♫No matter how much I say♫
♫ مهما قلت ♫
♫Thousand years of reincarnation is too confusing♫
♫ ألف سنة من التناسخ أمر محير للغاية ♫
♫I can't tell what character I'm playing♫
♫ لا أستطيع تحديد الشخصية التي ألعبها ♫
♫Closing my eyes♫
♫ أغلق عيني ♫
♫Reaching out and touching with my hands♫
مد يدها ولمسها بيدي ♫
♫Feeling your face based on memory♫
♫ تحسس وجهك بناء على الذاكرة ♫
Li Chengxi.
لي تشنغسي.
♫The mockery of fate, how difficult it is♫
استهزاء القدر ، ما مدى صعوبة ذلك
Don't go.
لا تذهب.
No.
لا.
♫Yearning is easily broken♫
♫ الحنين ينكسر بسهولة ♫
♫The more you want to escape♫
كلما أردت الهروب أكثر
♫The deeper the pain is♫
كلما كان الألم أعمق ♫
♫The tears try not to glisten♫
لا تحاول الدموع أن تتلألأ ♫
Li Chengxi.
لي تشنغسي.
Yan.
يان.
How are you feeling?
كيف تشعر؟
Do you have any discomfort?
هل تشعر بأي إزعاج؟
Young Master.
المعلم الصغير.
The purchase has arrived.
وصل الشراء.
We need you to take a look.
نحتاج منك أن تلقي نظرة.
You go ahead.
تفضل.
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Then you rest well.
ثم ترتاح جيدا.
Here.
هنا.
Are you really going to marry him
هل ستتزوجه حقًا؟
when you haven't retrieved your memory?
عندما لا تسترجع ذاكرتك؟
Are you thinking about Li Chengxi?
هل تفكر في Li Chengxi؟
No.
لا.
You can't fool me.
لا يمكنك أن تخدعني.
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
I used to be a very proud person.
اعتدت أن أكون شخصًا فخورًا جدًا.
There were so many people
كان هناك الكثير من الناس
who wanted to be my lovers.
من أراد أن يكون عشقي.
But I chose Li Chengxi.
لكنني اخترت Li Chengxi.
In order to get him,
من أجل الحصول عليه ،
I am even a little unscrupulous.
أنا حتى قليل الضمير.
But in his heart,
لكن في قلبه
there is always another girl.
هناك دائما فتاة أخرى.
Who can say for sure
من يستطيع أن يقول على وجه اليقين
about love?
عن الحب؟
Life
حياة
can be long
يمكن أن تكون طويلة
or short.
أو باختصار.
It's not easy for two lovebirds
ليس من السهل على طائرا حب
to be together.
لنكون معا.
Some people
بعض الناس
just make do with it.
فقط افعلها.
But if it's possible,
ولكن إذا كان ذلك ممكنًا ،
why don't you follow your heart?
لماذا لا تتبع قلبك
Can we
هل نستطيع
postpone our wedding?
تأجيل زفافنا؟
Yan.
يان.
We're getting married tomorrow.
سنتزوج غدا.
Why did you suddenly...
لماذا فجأة ...
Li Jian.
لي جيان.
I've always believed that
لطالما آمنت بذلك
you were my destined one.
كنت قدري.
I should marry you.
يجب أن أتزوجك.
But now that I think about it,
ولكن الآن بعد أن فكرت في الأمر ،
I was being too selfish.
كنت أناني جدا.
You are not a tool
أنت لست أداة
to cure my blood vessel disease.
لعلاج مرض الأوعية الدموية.
I shouldn't
لا يجب
marry you
أتزوجك
just because you are my destined one,
فقط لأنك قدري ،
but
لكن
we have to love each other from the bottom of our hearts.
علينا أن نحب بعضنا البعض من أعماق قلوبنا.
But...
لكن...
I do love you from the bottom of my heart.
أحبك من أعماق قلبي.
Besides,
بجانب،
I never thought I was your tool.
لم اعتقد ابدا انني كنت اداتك.
I'm willing to
أنا على استعداد ل
let you use me to solve your problem.
تتيح لك استخدامي لحل مشكلتك.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I promised to marry you,
لقد وعدت بالزواج منك ،
but now I have to go back on my word.
ولكن الآن علي أن أعود إلى كلامي.
But I really appreciate you
لكنني أقدر لك حقًا
for helping me with my disease.
لمساعدتي في مرضي.
But
لكن
I can't remember anything.
لا أستطيع تذكر أي شيء.
For me now,
بالنسبة لي الآن ،
we've only known each other for a few days.
عرفنا بعضنا البعض فقط لبضعة أيام.
Can you
هل تستطيع
give me more time
تعطيني المزيد من الوقت
to really fall in love with you
أن تقع في حبك حقًا
before we get married?
قبل ان نتزوج
But
لكن
your blood vessel disease...
مرض الأوعية الدموية ...
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
Li Chengxi told me
قال لي Chengxi لي
that if I can find the second half of the Book of Yueque,
أنه إذا تمكنت من العثور على النصف الثاني من كتاب يويكي ،
maybe
ربما
it can cure me.
يمكن أن يعالجني.
What if you can't find it?
ماذا لو لم تجده؟
The doctor said
وقال الطبيب
you only have three months to live.
لديك ثلاثة أشهر فقط للعيش.
Do you know
هل تعرف
you're playing with your life?
أنت تلعب بحياتك؟
Giving up before I find it.
استسلم قبل أن أجده.
This is not my style.
هذا ليس أسلوبي.
In that case,
في هذه الحالة،
I'll listen to you.
سوف استمع اليك.
Put this over there.
ضع هذا هناك.
[Happiness]
[سعادة]
Miss Tang.
ملكة جمال تانغ.
Ruoyu?
رويو؟
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
Didn't Li Jian tell you?
ألم يخبرك لي جيان؟
We agreed yesterday
اتفقنا أمس
to suspend the wedding.
لتعليق الزفاف.
Well...
حسنًا...
I really don't know.
أنا حقا لا أعرف.
But you are so determined to find your destined one.
لكنك مصمم جدًا على العثور على الشخص الذي تريده.
Now that you've found him,
الآن بعد أن وجدته ،
why did you give up?
لماذا استسلمت
Look at these accessories as well as your wedding gown.
انظر إلى هذه الإكسسوارات وكذلك ثوب الزفاف الخاص بك.
They are so beautiful.
إنهن بغاية الجمال.
They are all made specially for you.
كلها مصنوعة خصيصا لك.
Here.
هنا.
Let me dress you up.
دعني ألبسك
No need.
لا حاجة.
No.
لا.
Ruoyu!
رويو!
Yan.
يان.
Ruoyu told me
قال لي Ruoyu
that you came around to the idea last night.
أنك توصلت إلى الفكرة الليلة الماضية.
You don't want to delay the wedding.
أنت لا تريد تأجيل الزفاف.
As planned,
كما خطط له،
we'll get married today.
سنتزوج اليوم.
Great.
عظيم.
Have you really come around?
هل أتيت حقًا؟
Mr. Li.
السيد.  لي.
Manager Shen.
مدير شين.
Let Miss Tang change into her wedding gown.
دع الآنسة تانغ ترتدي ثوب زفافها.
Okay.
تمام.
Look at me.
انظر إليَّ.
I'm so happy.
انا سعيد للغاية.
Well,
حسنًا،
you get changed first.
أنت تتغير أولا.
My cousin and I will wait for you outside.
أنا وابن عمي سننتظرك بالخارج.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Go!
يذهب!
Hurry up.
أسرع - بسرعة.
[Happiness]
[سعادة]
♫Is it right or wrong to let go♫
♫ هل من الصواب أو الخطأ ترك
♫With a heart beating warm but pretending to be cold♫
بقلب ينبض دافئًا لكنه يتظاهر بالبرودة ♫
A bow to heaven and earth.
قوس للسماء والأرض.
♫Whether I lose you or keep you♫
♫ سواء خسرتك أو احتفظت بك
♫We can't escape the torture♫
لا نستطيع الهروب من التعذيب ♫
A second bow to parents.
القوس الثاني للوالدين.
♫Your figure is very thin♫
♫ شكلك نحيف جدا ♫
♫Choking up, I look even weaker♫
♫ الاختناق ، أبدو أضعف
[Memorial Tablet of my late brother Tang Sishi]
[لوح تذكاري لأخي الراحل تانغ سيشي]
And bow to each other.
وانحني لبعضنا البعض.
♫It won't help♫
♫ لن يساعد ♫
♫No matter how much I say♫
♫ مهما قلت ♫
Wait.
انتظر.
Li Chengxi.
لي تشنغسي.
Today is my wedding day with Yan.
اليوم هو يوم زفافي مع يان.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Li Chengxi.
لي تشنغسي.
Don't go too far.
لا تذهب بعيدا.
Yan and I are in love.
يان وأنا في حالة حب.
Don't make trouble here.
لا تجعل المتاعب هنا.
You are in love?
أنت واقع في الحب؟
Do you dare tell Yan in her face
هل تجرؤ على إخبار يان في وجهها
that you have a clear conscience about this wedding?
أن لديك ضمير مرتاح بشأن هذا الزفاف؟
I did bribe the physician.
لقد قمت برشوة الطبيب.
So what?
وماذا في ذلك؟
You kept harassing Yan.
لقد واصلت مضايقة يان.
Only in this way
بهذه الطريقة فقط
can I make you let her be.
هل يمكنني أن أجعلك تدعها تكون.
Let us be.
فلنكن.
Where am I?
أين أنا؟
This...
هذا...
Well...
حسنًا...
Didn't we agree not to get married?
ألم نتفق على عدم الزواج؟
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
Boss.
رئيس.
You were compelled?
كنت مجبرا؟
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
I just
أنا فقط
feel a little dizzy.
تشعر بقليل من الدوار.
How did it happen?
كيف حدث ذلك؟
What the hell is going on here?
ما يجري بحق الجحيم هنا؟
Yan had been determined to postpone the wedding,
كان يان مصممًا على تأجيل الزفاف ،
but she suddenly changed her mind this morning.
لكنها غيرت رأيها فجأة هذا الصباح.
During this period,
خلال هذه الفترة،
there must have been someone who did it to her on purpose.
يجب أن يكون هناك شخص ما فعل ذلك لها عن قصد.
Yan.
يان.
I didn't do it.
أنا لم أفعل ذلك.
How could I do such a thing?
كيف يمكنني فعل شيء كهذا؟
Why did you do that?
لماذا فعلت ذلك؟
Young Master,
المعلم الصغير،
are you asking me?
هل تسالني؟
Of course, I'm asking you.
بالطبع ، أنا أسألك.
Why did you compel Yan?
لماذا أرغمت يان؟
Young Master.
المعلم الصغير.
There must be some misunderstanding.
يجب أن يكون هناك بعض سوء الفهم.
I didn't compel
لم أجبر
Miss Tang.
ملكة جمال تانغ.
I saw you sneaking around
رأيتك تتسلل
and eavesdropping outside Li Jian's room last night.
والتنصت خارج غرفة لي جيان الليلة الماضية.
I knew
كنت أعلم
you must be up to something.
يجب أن تكون على وشك شيء ما.
So I decided to
لذلك قررت
wait and see.
انتظر و شاهد.
I didn't expect that Yan would suddenly chang her mind
لم أكن أتوقع أن تغير يان رأيها فجأة
and decide to get married today,
وتقرر الزواج اليوم ،
after you brought the wedding gown
بعد أن أحضرت ثوب الزفاف
to Yan's room
إلى غرفة يان
and tidied her hair.
ورتبت شعرها.
I'm sure
أنا متأكد
you're the reason
انت السبب
Yan suddenly changed her mind.
فجأة غيرت يان رأيها.
I just noticed her eyes were lifeless.
لقد لاحظت للتو عينيها هامدة.
So I knew
لذلك علمت
you had done something to her.
لقد فعلت شيئًا لها.
Now I have the witness and evidence.
الآن لدي الشاهد والأدلة.
What else do you want to say?
ماذا تريد ان تقول ايضا؟
Young Master, I didn't.
سيد الشباب ، لم أفعل.
It's all a coincidence.
إنها مصادفة.
Coincidence?
صدفة؟
When I tried to wake up Yan's memory,
عندما حاولت إيقاظ ذاكرة يان ،
you destroyed my plans.
لقد دمرت خططي.
How would you explain that?
كيف تفسر ذلك؟
Who ordered you to do this?
من أمرك بفعل هذا؟
Young Master.
المعلم الصغير.
For all these years,
لكل هذه السنوات ،
you really can't
أنت حقا لا تستطيع
feel my feelings for you at all?
أشعر بمشاعري تجاهك على الإطلاق؟
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
No one ordered me to do it.
لم يأمرني أحد للقيام بذلك.
I just don't want you to marry another woman.
أنا فقط لا أريدك أن تتزوج امرأة أخرى.
No matter if it's Shen Yi or Tang Buyan,
لا يهم إذا كانت شين يي أو تانغ بويان ،
they both can't.
كلاهما لا يستطيع.
That's why I forced Tang Buyan to marry Li Jian.
لهذا السبب أجبرت تانغ بويان على الزواج من لي جيان.
Because only when they are together
لأنه فقط عندما يكونون معًا
can I dispel all of your thoughts about her.
هل يمكنني تبديد كل أفكارك عنها.
Only then can you belong to me.
عندها فقط يمكنك أن تنتمي لي.
You can only
تستطيع فقط
belong to me.
أنه ملكي.
At this point,
عند هذه النقطة،
you still want to hide it from me?
هل مازلت تريد إخفاءه عني؟
When did you learn the sorcery to control people's minds?
متى تعلمت السحر للسيطرة على عقول الناس؟
Why didn't I know?
لماذا لم اعرف؟
Ruoyu.
رويو.
You grew up on Xuanqi Mountain
لقد نشأت في جبل Xuanqi
with me and Xue.
معي و Xue.
I don't believe
أنا لا أعتقد
you would hurt others
سوف تؤذي الآخرين
for your own benefit.
لمصلحتك الخاصة.
If you have any difficulties,
إذا واجهت أي صعوبات ،
you can tell me.
بإمكانك أن تخبرني.
We can solve it together.
يمكننا حلها معًا.
Ruoyu.
رويو.
You...
أنت...
Sir.
سيد.
I had no choice.
لم يكن لدي اي خيار.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Love
حب
is fake.
مزيف.
But my feelings toward you
لكن مشاعري تجاهك
and Second Master
والماجستير الثاني
are real.
حقيقة.
If there is a next life,
إذا كانت هناك حياة أخرى ،
I hope…
آمل…
Ruoyu…
رويو ...
She is also a pitiful girl.
وهي أيضا فتاة يرثى لها.
Yan.
يان.
It's all my fault
هذا كله خطأي
that you got hurt by Ruoyu.
أن Ruoyu تأذيت.
Although Ruoyu
على الرغم من Ruoyu
compelled you,
اضطررت لك ،
this wedding is my wish.
هذا العرس هو أمنيتي.
Since we've already bowed to each other,
منذ انحنينا لبعضنا البعض
why don't we
لماذا لا نفعل
continue the wedding?
اكمل العرس؟
I told you last night
لقد أخبرتك الليلة الماضية
that we would get married.
أننا سوف نتزوج.
But not now.
لكن ليس الآن.
Besides,
بجانب،
I've decided
لقد قررت
to go to the Serene Valley with Li Chengxi
للذهاب إلى Serene Valley مع Li Chengxi
to find the Book of Yueque.
للعثور على كتاب Yueque.
Yan.
يان.
Have you really decided to
هل حقا قررت
go to the valley with me?
اذهب الى الوادي معي؟
Maybe it can cure my disease.
ربما يمكن أن يعالج مرضي.
Okay.
تمام.
I'll definitely help you.
سأساعدك بالتأكيد.
Yan.
يان.
Today's wedding
زفاف اليوم
is all my fault.
هو كل خطأي.
If I had found out earlier,
إذا اكتشفت ذلك سابقًا ،
we wouldn't have ended up like this.
لم نكن لننتهي بهذا الشكل.
Li Jian.
لي جيان.
You don't have to blame yourself.
ليس عليك أن تلوم نفسك.
It's not your fault.
انها ليست غلطتك.
Yan.
يان.
I've made up my mind.
أنا إتخذت قراري.
I'm willing to wait for you
أنا على استعداد لانتظارك
until the day
حتي اليوم
you really want to marry me.
أنت حقا تريد الزواج مني.
You want to go to the Serene Valley.
تريد الذهاب إلى وادي سيرين.
I'll come with you.
سآتي معك.
I'm fine though.
أنا بخير رغم ذلك.
Just...
فقط...
Yan.
يان.
You don't know.
أنت لا تعرف.
The Serene Valley is very dangerous.
وادي سيرين خطير جدا.
Once people outside the valley enter it, they may never come out alive.
بمجرد دخول الناس خارج الوادي ، قد لا يخرجون أحياء.
If you have one more person with you,
إذا كان لديك شخص آخر معك ،
it will be safer.
سيكون أكثر أمانًا.
No need.
لا حاجة.
I'll protect Yan myself.
سأحمي يان بنفسي.
Li Chengxi is really skilled at martial arts.
لي Chengxi ماهر حقًا في فنون الدفاع عن النفس.
But there are puppets
لكن هناك دمى
made by the Lord of the Serene Valley
صنعه رب وادي سيرين
in there.
هناك.
They will attack those who trespass into the valley.
سوف يهاجمون أولئك الذين يتعدون على الوادي.
No matter how skilled he is,
بغض النظر عن مدى مهارته ،
he can't resist so many puppets.
لا يستطيع مقاومة الكثير من الدمى.
I
أنا
used to spend some time in the valley,
كان يقضي بعض الوقت في الوادي ،
and I am familiar with the valley.
وأنا على دراية بالوادي.
So I also know how to control puppets.
لذلك أعرف أيضًا كيفية التحكم في الدمى.
I can definitely help you.
يمكنني بالتأكيد مساعدتك.
Really?
حقًا؟
But
لكن
the Serene Valley does not allow outsiders to enter.
لا يسمح وادي سيرين للأجانب بالدخول.
How did you get in?
كيف تحصل في؟
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
the Lord of the valley
رب الوادي
is
يكون
my mother.
أمي.
Really?
حقًا؟
If that's the case you should definitely come with us.
إذا كان هذا هو الحال ، يجب أن تأتي معنا بالتأكيد.
Maybe
ربما
we can find the Book of Yueque without any effort.
يمكننا العثور على كتاب Yueque دون أي جهد.
In that case,
في هذه الحالة،
we'll set out tomorrow.
سننطلق غدا.
Be careful.
احرص.
The puppets in the valley are very dangerous.
الدمى في الوادي خطيرة للغاية.
[Serene Valley]
[وادي سيرين]
They are coming.
انهم قادمون.
Why are we so unlucky?
لماذا نحن غير محظوظين؟
We met them right after we came in.
التقينا بهم بعد دخولنا مباشرة.
Watch out!
احترس!
Li Jian.
لي جيان.
Is this the danger you mentioned?
هل هذا هو الخطر الذي ذكرته؟
You made moves before I could finish.
لقد قمت بحركات قبل أن أنتهي.
But
لكن
the fun is yet to come.
المرح لم يأت بعد.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
That color represents farming.
هذا اللون يمثل الزراعة.
What do these two colors represent?
ماذا يمثل هذان اللونان؟
Are they
هل هم
servants?
خدم؟
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
That group of puppets was so stupid just now.
كانت تلك المجموعة من الدمى في غاية الغباء الآن.
Why are they so fierce?
لماذا هم بهذه الشراسة؟
The puppets in earth-colored clothes just now
الدمى في ملابس ملونة للتو
are quite low-class.
هي فئة منخفضة للغاية.
They are not aggressive.
هم ليسوا عدوانيين.
They just do some odd jobs in the valley
إنهم يقومون ببعض الأعمال الغريبة في الوادي
and are easier to control.
وأسهل في التحكم.
And these ones in red and green clothes
وهؤلاء الذين يرتدون ملابس حمراء وخضراء
should be the more advanced ones that she has developed,
يجب أن تكون الأكثر تقدمًا التي طورتها ،
which are more aggressive.
أيهما أكثر عدوانية.
But
لكن
your mother really has nothing better to do.
والدتك حقا ليس لديها شيء أفضل لتفعله.
She developed so many kinds of puppets.
لقد طورت أنواعًا كثيرة من الدمى.
Luckily, you can control them.
لحسن الحظ ، يمكنك التحكم بهم.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Li Chengxi, watch out!
Li Chengxi ، احترس!
Why are they suddenly going crazy?
لماذا يصابون بالجنون فجأة؟
Tell them to stop!
قل لهم أن يتوقفوا!
I don't know why
أنا لا أعرف لماذا
they suddenly lost control.
فقدوا السيطرة فجأة.
Maybe what I learned before
ربما ما تعلمته من قبل
has been improved by her.
تم تحسينها بواسطتها.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I'll figure something out.
سأعرف شيئا.
Be careful, Li Chengxi!
كن حذرا ، لى تشنغشى!
The valley is too dangerous.
الوادي خطير جدا.
Let's go find
دعنا نذهب للبحث
Brother Yan and Xue first.
الأخ يان وشوي أولاً.
That's right.
صحيح.
Let's hurry up and find
دعنا نسرع ​​ونجد
the mark you mentioned.
العلامة التي ذكرتها.
By the way, what does the mark look like?
بالمناسبة ، كيف تبدو العلامة؟
It looks like Wushan.
يبدو مثل Wushan.
Wushan?
وشان؟
What is Wushan?
ما هو وشان؟
When I was fighting,
عندما كنت أقاتل ،
I saw their mark on the tree.
رأيت بصماتهم على الشجرة.
Here!
هنا!
This thing looks so strange!
هذا الشيء يبدو غريبا جدا!